Guide to the Jerald Brauer Papers 1925-1999
University of Chicago Library
- Series III: Federated Theological Faculty. 1943-1960
  - B.D. Degree, Resource Book, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - B.D. Committee (old program), 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - B.D. Committee Minutes, 1951-1954 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - B.D. Committee, Minutes and Exams, 1951-1956 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - B.D. Committee Minutes, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - B.D. Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - B.D. Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - B.D. Committee, Resource Book for Parish Training Program, part II. History, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - B.D. Committee, Resource Book for Parish Training Program, part III. Interns, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - B.D. Committee, Resource Book for Parish Training Program, part IV B. D. Programs, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - B.D. Committee, Resource Book for Parish Training Program, part V. Agenda, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - B.D. Committee, Resource Book for Parish Training Program, misc. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - B.D. Committee Correspondence, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Board of Social Missions, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Board of Social Missions, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Budget, Ministerial Housing Allowance, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary, 1963-1964 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary/FTF Discussions, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Carby, Jim, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Christian Action, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Church and Economic Life, 1948-1952 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Church Federation of Greater Chicago, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Church Federation of Greater Chicago, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Clinical Pastoral Education, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - The College and the Divinity School, 1950-1953 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Cooperation Between the Seminaries, 1942-1943 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Cooperation, Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Cooperation, n. d. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Cooperation, drafts, n. d. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Cooperation, Earlier Agreements, n. d. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Cooperation, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary (CTS) Presidency, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - CTS, 1954-1960 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Expenses, FTF, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Catalog Requests, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Chicago Sunday Evening Club, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Committee of the Student Government, The Chicago Review, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Ministry, 1952-1953 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Community Fund of Chicago, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Community Fund of Chicago, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Community Fund of Chicago, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Conference House, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Congratulations from FTF, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Counseling Center, 1954-1955 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Center for the Study of Christian World Missions, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Center for the Study of Christian World Mission, n. d. (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Crank letters, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Crank letters, 1939-1952 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Crank letters, 1956-1958 (and see Oversize BOX 184, Folder 2) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Crank letters, n. d. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Crank letters, published literature, n. d. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - CTS, Board of Directors, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - CTS, President, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - CTS, Schomer Inauguration, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - CTS, Replogle Correspondence, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Deanship, Committee on, 1953-1954 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Dean's Report, FTF, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Defederation, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Defederation, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Defederation, 1951-1960 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Degree Program, A.M., n. d. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Degree Program, D.D., n. d. (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Development, 1956-1958 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Disciples Divinity House, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Divinity School, 1944-1945 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Divinity School, 1943-1944 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Divinity School, 1942-1943 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Downtown College, correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Ecumenical Institute (The Evanston Institute for Ecumenical Studies), correspondence and minutes, 1952-1957 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Ecumenical Institute, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Engagements accepted, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Engagements refused, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Engagements refused, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Engagements refused, 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Examinations, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Examination Report Blanks, n. d. (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Executive Committee on Undergraduate Education, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Biographical Materials,, 1954-1957 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Christian Fellowship, 1956-1957 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Faculty List, n. d. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Meetings (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Meeting, Minutes, 1938-1941 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Program Schedules, 1944-1945 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Program Schedules, 1945-1946 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Program Schedules, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Program Schedules, 1947-1948 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Program Schedules, 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - FTF, Bylaw Proposal, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - FTF, Bylaws, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - FTF, B.D. Notes, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - FTF, Cabinet Minutes, 1940s (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - FTF, Cabinet Minutes, 1950s (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - FTF, Cabinet Minutes, 1950s (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - FTF, Clippings, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - FTF, Church History, 1944-1956 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - FTF, Correspondence, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - FTF, Fields, Biblical, 1955-1957 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - FTF, Fields, Christian Theology, 1954-1955 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - FTF, Future of FTF, n. d. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - FTF, Lecture Committee, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - FTF, Hutchins and FTF, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - FTF, Inauguration, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - FTF, Inaugural Address, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - FTF, Interboard Academic, 1954-1958 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - FTF, Faculty Minutes, 1940s (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - FTF, Faculty Minutes, 1940s (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - FTF, Faculty Minutes, 1950s (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - FTF, Faculty Minutes, 1950s (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - FTF, Minutes, 1949-1955 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - FTF, Papers and Articles, 1951-1952 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - FTF and Robert Hutchins, 1943-1957 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - FTF, Inter-Board Academic, 1954-1958 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - FTF, Plans, Strategic, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - FTF, Plans, Strategic, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - FTF, Policy Committee, 1954-1956 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - FTF, Promotional Materials and Conference, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - FTF, Proposals, 1955-1959 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - FTF, Proposed Degree Programs, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Fellowship, Christian Frontier, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Field, Church History, 1948-1957 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Field, Ethics and Society, 1952-1958 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Field, History of Christianity, 1955-1957 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Field, History of Religions, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Field, Religion and Art, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Field, Religion and Personality, 1957-1958 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Field, Practical, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Four Schools, Interboard Committee, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary, 1957-1959 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Divinity School News, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Disciples Divinity House, 1955-1958 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Disciples of Divinity, Students, 1943-1954 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Studies in Religion, 1951-1957 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Graham Crusade, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - H.R. Study Center, n. d. (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Home Study, 1941-1951 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Home Study, Personnel, 1941-1943 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Hoover Lectureship, 1957-1958 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Hospital Chaplaincy, 1944-1952 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Internships, 1953-1960 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Institute, Behavioral Sciences, 1951 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Institute for Advanced Pastoral Studies, 1957-1959 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Interchurch Center, n. d. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Chautauqua Society, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Journal of Religion, 1950-1958 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Kentucky Council of Churches, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Library, Program Statement, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Library, Divinity School, 1956-1957 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Lutheran Seminar, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Meadville Proposal, 1959-1960 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Ministerial Students, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - National Council of Churches Newsletter, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Manuscripts, n. d. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - M.R.E., n. d (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Missions, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Missions Research Center, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Missions, Publications and Reports, 1952-1953 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Missions, Inter-religious/ Intercultural Program, 1953-1954 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Missions, Intercultural, 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Mission Report, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Mission House Theological Seminary, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Missions, Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Missions Proposal, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Missions, Publications and Reports, 1952-1953 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Missions Research Center, 1956-1959 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Meadville Inauguration, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Meadville Theological Seminary, 1942-1958 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - National Council of Churches, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Nature of the Church, 1951-1952 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Nef, John, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Ohio Council of Churches, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Orientation Meetings, 1951-1960 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Orientation Sequence, n. d. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Parish Field, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Papers and Articles, Non-FTF Members, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Papers and Articles, Non-FTF Members, 1954-1966 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Parish Training Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Parish Training, B.D. Program, 1957-1958 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Patent Policies, 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Petty Cash, 1956-1957 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Policy Committee, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Positions, Churches, 1957-1959 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - PhD. Candidates, n. d. (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Quadrennial Convocation of Christian Colleges Address, n. d. (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Quadrennial Convocation, Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Qualifying Exams, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Qualifying Exams, Questions, 1950-1951 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Quest Journal, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Quest Journal Budget, 1957-1970 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Radio Advisory Committee, 1944-1953 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Radio Workshop, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Rauschenbusch Commemoration, 1957-1958 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - The Registrar's Report to the President, 1938-1939 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - The Registrar's Report to the President, 1939-1940 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - The Registrar's Report to the President, 1940-1941 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - The Registrar's Report to the President, 1941-1942 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - The Registrar's Report to the President 1942-1943 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Reports FTF, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Religion and Agriculture, research proposal and correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Religion and Art, Field Exams, 1956 and n. d. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Religion and Art, Goodman Theater, Downtown College, playbills, reports, press releases, correspondence, course syllabus, 1957-1958 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Religion and Health, correspondence and article regarding new professorship, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Religion in Higher Education, correspondence 1950-1952, regarding conference (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Religion Faces the Atomic Age, February 2-3, 1958, press release, flyer, notes on speakers (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Religion Faces the Atomic Age, correspondence with speakers and participants, 1957-1958 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, follow-up correspondence and press clippings, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, "Portrait of God," transcript from television show, on the occasion of Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, Bauer, "Religion Faces the Space Age," presented at Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, 1958, printed in Advance, March 14,1958 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, Hiltner, Seward, "Facing the Fears of the Atomic Age," paper presented at Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, Kimpton, Lawrence A., "Religion Faces the Atomic Age," paper presented at Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, Logelin, Edward C., "Religion and its Role in the World of Business," paper presented at Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, Marshner, Robert F., "What Should Christianity Expect of Public Education Today?," paper presented at Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, Miller, Alexander, "Christianity and Communism; Two Faiths in Conflict," paper presented at Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, Murphy, Gardner, "Face those Atomic Fears!" presented at Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, 1958, printed in The Christian Century, Feb 26, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, Nuveen, John, "Christianity and Communism; Two Faiths in Conflict," paper presented at Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, Taft, Charles P., "Religion Faces the Atomic Age," paper presented at Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, Urey, Harold C., "Religion Faces the Atomic Age," paper presented at Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, Utley, Frayn, "What Should Religion Demand of Public Education Today?," paper presented at Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, Worthy, James C., "Religion and Its Role in the World of Business," paper presented at Religion Faces the Atomic Age Conference, 1958, printed in Chicago Theological Seminary Register, Vol 48, No 3, April 1958 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Religious Education Association, National Convention, 1956-1957 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Religious, Education Association, 1956-1958 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Retirement, memo on policy, 1956-1959 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Reviews, University of Chicago Press, n. d. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Schomer Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - School Constitutions, FTF, 1953-1958 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Sealantic Fund, 1955-1957 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Sealantic Fund, 1955-1958 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Sealantic Proposition, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Sealantic Proposition, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Seminar for Mission Executives, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Senexet Conference, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Sixteen Point Program, n. d. (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Suenens Correspondence, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Summer Seminar, miscellaneous correspondence, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Social Science-Theology Faculty Seminar, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Social Security, regarding status of Ministers, 1950-1955 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Social Security, regarding status of Ministers, 1956-1958 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Social Mission, Board of, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Social Missions Quarterly, 1957-1958 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1957-1958 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Speaking Engagements, Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Stecker, Reverend B.J., 1958 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Swan, Albert, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Theology and Literature, Course Materials, Preston Roberts, Instructor, 1951-1957 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Theology and Literature, Course Materials, Nathan A. Scott, Jr., Instructor, 1955-1958 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Travel, 1950s (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - U Win, Burmese Ambassador to the United States, May 27-28, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate Education Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - University College, 1949-1959 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - University Senate, 1957-1958 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - University Senate, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - USCF at University of New Mexico, 1955-1956 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Vanderhoof, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Vatican II, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Wach Memorial Publication, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Wach, Joachim, Sermon, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - West Side Christian Parish, 1956-1957 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Roger Williams Fellowship, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Series IV: Divinity School. 1960-1985
  Series IV: Divinity School contains two subseries: Subseries 1, Subject Files and Subseries 2, Faculty Materials. Many of the files in Subseries 1 deal with the administration of the Divinity School where Brauer was dean from 1960 through 1970. Other files include material on groups, organizations, committees, and universities with ties to Brauer. The files contain a significant amount of information relating to student activism and protest on the University of Chicago Campus in the late 1960s. The visit of Cardinal Suenens to campus in 1964, is also well documented in the collection.
  Subseries 2, Faculty Materials consists primarily of unpublished academic papers written by divinity school faculty. The paper are arranged alphabetically by author within the series.
  - Subseries 1: Subject Files
    - Agenda Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Aid Association for Lutherans, 1974-1981 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Air Travel Card, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Alumni, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - American Academy of Religion, 1975-1977 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - American Census, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - American Civilization Program, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - American Society for Church History, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - American Studies Seminar, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Arts, Religon, and Contemporary Culture, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - American Association of Theological Schools, 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Archive Project, n. d. (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Arizona State University, 1972-1978 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Arthritis Clippings, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Associated Theological Faculties, n. d. (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - American Baptist Convention, 1958-1960 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - American Baptist Convention, 1961-1968 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Anniversary Summary, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Audenshaw Documents, n. d. (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - B.D Committee Meetings and Miscellaneous B.D. Information Prior, to 1955 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - B.D. Committee Meeting, 1955-1960 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - B.D. Committee Meetings, 1960-1963 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - B.D. Committee Meetings, 1964-1966 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - B.D. Students (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - B.D. Materials, 1961, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Bioethics, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Bioethics, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Bioethics, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - B'Nai B'rith Foundation, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Book Reviews (accepted), 1970 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Britannica, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - BTE, 1970 Report (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Budget Committee, Resource Manual, n. d. (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Cable Television, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Catholic Theological Union, 1967-1968 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Center for Church Music Proposal, n. d. (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Center for Continuing Education, 1960-1967 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Center for Policy Studies, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Center for Urban Studies, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Chaplaincy, Institutional (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Chaplaincy, U.S. Army, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Chaplaincy, U.S. Army, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Chaplaincy, U.S. Army, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Chaplaincy, U.S. Army, 1961-1965 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Chapel, Rockefeller, 1959-1957 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Chautaugua, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Chicago Institute for Advanced Theological Studies, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Chimera, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Christian Century, 1960-1963 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Christian Action, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Church and China, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Church and State, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Church Federation of Greater Chicago, 1958-1964 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Clippings, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Advancing the Democratic Process, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Social Thought, 1961-1964 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Consultation on the Role of Campus Ministry, n. d. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Center for the Comparative Study of Religion, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Conference on Radiation and Social Ethics, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Controversy, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Coordinating Committee on Religious Thought, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Criterion, 1965-1969 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Criterion, 1964-1968 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Commission on Women's Year, 1975-1976 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Commission on Women's Year, 1975-1976 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Committee, Divinity School Evaluation, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Computation Center, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Council of the Study of Mankind, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Council on Graduate Studies in Religion, 1960-1968 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Convocation Speech Requests, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Council of the University Senate, 1977-1979 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Council on the Future, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Council on the Study of Religion, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Criterion, 1969-1970 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Dean's Report, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Dean, Office of, 1963-1970 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Dean's Report, Baptist Theological Union, 1959-1970 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Deanship Committee,, n. d (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Divinity School Reconstitution, n. d. (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Defense Fellowship, 1958-1963 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Development Plans, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Development Pamphlets, n. d. (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Dialog, 1964-1972 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Divinity School Alumni, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Divinity School, Course Materials (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Divinity School, Bylaws, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Divinity School, Appointment Guidelines (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Divinity School, Essays and Notes (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Divinity School, Field Requirements (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Divinity School, Article (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Divinity School, Essays (Box 46, Folder 6)